<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SystemUI Tuner</string>
    <string name="manager_channel">Hanterare (stäng av)</string>
    <string name="tap_to_disable">Tryck för att inaktivera denna avisering</string>
    <string name="home">Startsida</string>
    <string name="category_display">Bildskärm</string>
    <string name="category_accessibility">Tillgänglighet</string>
    <string name="category_apps">Appar</string>
    <string name="category_audio">Ton &amp; Ljud</string>
    <string name="category_developer">Utvecklare</string>
    <string name="category_easter_eggs">Påskägg</string>
    <string name="category_network">Nätverk</string>
    <string name="category_notifications">Aviseringar</string>
    <string name="category_status_bar">Statusfält</string>
    <string name="category_oem">OEM-funktioner</string>
    <string name="category_system">System</string>
    <string name="category_ui">Gränssnitt</string>
    <string name="category_lock_screen">Låsskärm</string>
    <string name="category_quick_settings">Snabbinställningar</string>
    <string name="screen_persistent">Beständiga alternativ</string>
    <string name="category_interaction">Interaktion</string>
    <string name="more">Mera</string>
    <string name="tweaks">Justeringar</string>
    <string name="failure">Fel</string>
    <string name="help_translate">Hjälp till med översättning</string>
    <string name="sub_cellular">Mobilt Nätverk</string>
    <string name="sub_wifi">Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="sub_miscellaneous">Blandat</string>
    <string name="sub_htc">HTC</string>
    <string name="sub_huawei">Huawei/Honor</string>
    <string name="sub_lg">LG</string>
    <string name="sub_oneplus">OnePlus</string>
    <string name="sub_samsung">Samsung</string>
    <string name="sub_sony">Sony</string>
    <string name="sub_xiaomi">Xiaomi</string>
    <string name="sub_security">Säkerhet</string>
    <string name="sub_storage">Lagring</string>
    <string name="sub_power">Ström</string>
    <string name="add_to_blacklist">Lägg till i svartlistan</string>
    <string name="remove_from_blacklist">Ta bort från svartlistan</string>
    <string name="flashlight">Ficklampa</string>
    <string name="sub_demo">Demoläge</string>
    <string name="sub_demo_desc">Demoläge låter dig tvinga in enhetens statusfält i olika stater. Du kan använda den för att visa eller dölja specifika ikoner, ange signalstyrkor, och några andra saker.</string>
    <string name="special_sub_airplane_mode">Anpassningar till Flygplansläget</string>
    <string name="special_sub_airplane_mode_desc">Flygplansläge inaktiverar automatiskt alla radioapparater på din enhet när den är aktiverad. Du kan ange vilka radioapparater som ska inaktiveras (till exempel att behålla WiFi när flygplansläget aktiveras). Du kan också ändra vilka radioapparater som kan växlas manuellt när enheten går in i flygplansläget.</string>
    <string name="special_sub_icon_blacklist">Svartlista</string>
    <string name="special_sub_icon_blacklist_desc">Välj specifika ikoner att dölja från statusfältet. Observera att denna funktion inte fungerar på alla enheter eller med alla ikoner. Notifikationsikoner kan inte döljas med den här funktionen.</string>
    <string name="feature_lock_timeout">Ange anpassad tidsgräns för låset</string>
    <string name="feature_lock_timeout_desc">Under \"säkra låsinställningar\" kan du ställa in en \"automatiskt låstidsgräns\". Denna tidsgräns bestämmer hur länge efter att enheten går in i viloläge som låsskärmen ska visas. Genom detta alternativ, kan du ställa in vilket värde (i millisekunder) som du vill. Om du anger ett tillräckligt högt värde, då kommer din låsskärm aldrig att visas (förutsatt att du har inaktiverat funktionen \"avstängningsknappen låser enheten direkt).</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_saver_trigger">Ställ in anpassad procentvärdet för batterisparläget att aktiveras</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_saver_trigger_desc" formatted="false">Googles batterisparfunktion kan automatiskt utlösas när batterinivån är på 5\% eller 15\%. Då kan du ställa in din egen utlösningsprocent.</string>
    <string name="feature_long_press_delay">Ställ in anpassad långtrycksfördröjning</string>
    <string name="feature_long_press_delay_desc">I Tillgänglighetsinställningar, det finns en funktion som heter \"Fördröjning för tryck och håll ned\" som låter dig ange hur länge du måste hålla fingern på skärmen för att Android ska känna igen en långtryckshändelse. De enda alternativen som standard är dock bara \"kort\", \"medium\" och \"lång.\" Du kan ställa in din egen fördröjning.</string>
    <string name="feature_font_scale">Set Custom Font Scale</string>
    <string name="feature_font_scale_desc">Android allows you to set the size of the text shown on your device by specifying a system-wide font scale. This value is typically represented as \"small\", \"normal\", \"large\", \"huge\", and \"extra huge.\" However, you can set your own custom value.</string>
    <string name="feature_freeform">Enable Freeform Multiwindow</string>
    <string name="feature_freeform_desc">Whether to enable freeform multiwindow support. Requires reboot. Only works on Android 7.0+ devices.</string>
    <string name="feature_app_install_location">Set Default App Install Location</string>
    <string name="feature_app_install_location_desc">Default app install location. Choose which storage apps are installed to by default. Normally, apps themselves decide by specifying the value in the AndroidManifest, but you can choose to have them install to the adoptable storage medium if you want.</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_notifications">Heads Up Notification Toggle</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_notifications_desc">Toggle to globally enable or disable heads up notifications. Heads up notifications are the notifications that pop up at the top of the screen.</string>
    <string name="feature_insufficient_storage_warning">Bypass \"Insufficient Storage Available\" Warning</string>
    <string name="feature_insufficient_storage_warning_desc">When your device reaches a certain threshold value of available storage, Android displays a warning that your device has insufficient amounts of storage available. This can prevent you from installing new apps or updates. You can manually lower the threshold value to prevent this warning from showing.</string>
    <string name="feature_keep_screen_on">Keep the Device On when Plugged In</string>
    <string name="feature_keep_screen_on_desc">In Android\'s Developer Settings, you can select the option to keep the screen on when plugged into power. By default, this enables the feature for all power sources. You can specify which power sources you want to have your phone\'s screen to stay on.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_animation_scales">Set Custom Animation Scales</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_animation_scales_desc">In Android\'s Developer Settings, you can set animation scales to control the duration of animations. If the available options are too fast or slow for you, you can set custom values here.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_rotation">Lock Screen Orientation to Custom Value</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_rotation_desc">Most phones only allow you to lock your phone\'s screen orientation to Portrait mode. With this setting, you can lock screen orientation to any orientation. You will first have to disable auto-rotate before this will work.</string>
    <string name="feature_immersive_mode">Immersive Mode</string>
    <string name="feature_immersive_mode_desc">Most other applications that allow you to toggle immersive mode only have a few options: hide the navigation bar or hide the status bar. It\'s actually possible to set this on a per-app basis, in either whitelist or blacklist mode. Note that on Android 11 and above, this option is broken in AOSP and may no longer work on your device.</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_snooze_length">Heads-Up Notification Snooze Length</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_snooze_length_desc">Milliseconds after a heads up notification is pushed back before the app can interrupt again. (Default: 60 seconds).</string>
    <string name="feature_camera_gestures">Camera Gestures</string>
    <string name="feature_camera_gestures_desc">Enabling this may allow your phone to quickly launch the camera by double tapping the power button or flipping the phone between back and front.</string>
    <string name="feature_disable_safe_audio_warning">Disable Safe Audio Warning</string>
    <string name="feature_disable_safe_audio_warning_desc">EU regulations require smartphones to warn when going above certain volume levels (85dB). This warning must be shown once after every reboot or after 20 hours of continuous music playback. Use this setting to change how that warning behaves, or disable it entirely. Make sure to enable this setting in Persistent Options for it to stick.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_ui_sounds">Set Custom UI Sounds</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_ui_sounds_desc">Android has a lot of sounds for different parts of the UI. A lot of these can actually be changed to your own custom sounds. You just need to specify the file for Android to use.</string>
    <string name="feature_fix_tethering">Fix Tethering</string>
    <string name="feature_fix_tethering_desc">On some devices and Android versions, this may bypass carrier restrictions on tethering.</string>
    <string name="feature_shortcode_warning">Disable SMS Short Code Confirmation</string>
    <string name="feature_shortcode_warning_desc">When sending SMS to certain short codes, the system warns you that you may be charged a fee. You can disable that warning here.</string>
    <string name="feature_sms_limit">Custom SMS Limit</string>
    <string name="feature_sms_limit_desc">By default, Android limits you to sending 30 SMS every 30 minutes before bothering you with a pop-up notification. Using these two values, you can customize however many SMS you want to be able to send without being bothered.</string>
    <string name="feature_lockscreen_shortcuts">Lock Screen Shortcuts</string>
    <string name="feature_lockscreen_shortcuts_desc">Starting with Android Oreo Developer Preview 3, Google removed the ability to customize the lock screen shortcuts. However, the preference value can still be set manually.</string>
    <string name="feature_enable_adb">Enable ADB</string>
    <string name="feature_enable_adb_desc">Certain devices disable ADB automatically after a period of inactivity. Enable this option and set it as a Persistent Option to force-enable ADB.</string>
    <string name="feature_dark_mode">Enable Global Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="feature_dark_mode_desc">Android Pie and 10 introduced a global dark mode option, but this option has been part of Android for a while now. This option can enable dark mode in apps that support this feature (such as Instagram). A reboot may be required for changes to take effect.</string>
    <string name="feature_clock_seconds">Show Clock Seconds</string>
    <string name="feature_clock_seconds_desc">Enable seconds in the status bar clock. This won\'t work on all devices and configurations, including MIUI and One UI.</string>
    <string name="feature_dnd_in_volume">Do Not Disturb Toggle in Volume Indicator</string>
    <string name="feature_dnd_in_volume_desc">Allows you to toggle Do Not Disturb from the volume popup.</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_percent">Show Battery Percentage in Status Bar</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_percent_desc">Shows the current battery percentage in the battery icon on the status bar. May require root to activate.</string>
    <string name="feature_header_airplane_mode_radios">Exempt</string>
    <string name="feature_header_airplane_mode_toggleable_radios">Toggleable</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_ac">On AC Power</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_usb">On USB Power</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_wireless">On Wireless Power</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_dock">On Dock</string>
    <string name="option_animator_duration_scale">Animatörlängdsskala</string>
    <string name="option_window_animation_scale">Fönsteranimatörsskala</string>
    <string name="option_transition_animation_scale">Övergångsanimeringsskala</string>
    <string name="option_storage_threshold_percentage">Lagringsgränsvärde (Procent)</string>
    <string name="option_storage_threshold_max_bytes">Lagringsgränsvärde (Bytes)</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture_double_power">Dubbeltrycka strömknappen</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture">Gest</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture_twist">Vänd telefonen fram och tillbaka</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_cell">Mobilcell</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_bluetooth">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_wifi">WiFi</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_nfc">NFC</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_wimax">WiMax</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_internal">Intern Lagring</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_sd">SD-Kort</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_0">Porträtt</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_90">Liggande CCW</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_180">Inverterad Porträtt</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_270">Liggande CW</string>
    <string name="option_sms_limit_count">Max-Antal Skickade</string>
    <string name="option_sms_limit_interval">Tidsintervall</string>
    <string name="option_lockscreen_shortcut_left">Vänster genväg</string>
    <string name="option_lockscreen_shortcut_right">Höger genväg</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_dock">Bilbrygga</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_dock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen sätts i en bilbrygga.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_undock">Bilbrygga separeras</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_undock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen tas bort från en bilbrygga.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_dock">Skrivbordsstation</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_dock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen sätts i en skrivbordsstation.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_undock">Skrivbordsstation tas bort</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_undock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen tas bort från en skrivbordsstation.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_lock">Lås</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_lock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen låses.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_unlock">Lås upp</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_unlock_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen låses upp.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_low_battery">Lågt batteri</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_low_battery_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonens batteri tar slut.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_trusted">Betrodd</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_trusted_desc">Ljud som spelas när enheten går in i “betrodd” tillstånd utan att låsa upp.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_wireless_charging">Trådlös laddning</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_wireless_charging_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen laddas trådlöst.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_charging">Laddar</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_charging_desc">Ljud som spelas när telefonen laddas.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_disable_charging">Inaktivera ljud vid laddning</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_disable_charging_desc">Om du vill inaktivera ljudet som spelas när enheten börjar ladda.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_revoke_system_ui_permission">Systemgränssnittsbehörigheter</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_revoke_system_ui_permission_desc">För att ändra dessa alternativ krävs en omstart av System UI. Du måste också starta om System UI efter enhetens omstart. Det enklaste sättet att starta om System UI utan omstart är att återkalla behörigheten \"Telefon\". Tryck här för att hantera behörigheter.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_read_setting">Läs anpassade inställningar</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_read_setting_desc">Om du känner till nyckeln till en viss inställning kan du använda den för att se dess aktuella värde.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_write_setting">Write Custom Setting</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_write_setting_desc">If you have a particular setting you want to change that isn\'t part of SystemUI Tuner, you can set it here.</string>
    <string name="option_qqs_tiles">Quick Settings Header Count</string>
    <string name="option_qqs_tiles_desc">Android Nougat introduced a new quick settings feature, called the Quick Settings Header, that shows the first few quick settings tiles in a single row in the notification shade. Using this option, it\'s possible to increase or decrease the number of tiles shown in that row. This will not work on One UI.</string>
    <string name="option_oneui_clock_position">Clock Position</string>
    <string name="option_oneui_clock_position_desc">On Samsung\'s One UI (Android Pie or later), it\'s possible to change the status bar clock position. Good Lock\'s QuickStar will let you do it, but the options are sometimes limited depending on the device. You can use this to set it to left, middle, or right. Be aware that on One UI 2.0 (Android 10), you need QuickStar to be installed for this option to have an effect. To make this option persistent, enable Icon Blacklist in Persistent Options.</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_navbar_color">Navigation Bar Color</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_navbar_color_desc">On Samsung Experience and One UI it\'s possible to set the navigation bar color to your own custom color. Use this option to do that.</string>
    <string name="option_custom_notification_snooze_times">Custom Notification Snooze Times</string>
    <string name="option_custom_notification_snooze_times_desc">Android Oreo 8.1 introduced an option to snooze notifications. You can use this setting to set custom values for the snooze times.</string>
    <string name="option_night_mode">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="option_night_mode_desc">Android Nougat introduced a native option to tint the display yellow at night, aptly called Night Mode. It was further refined in Nougat 7.1, and renamed to Night Display. You can enable it here and adjust different options. WARNING: On some devices, activating this will cause the screen to go black!</string>
    <string name="night_display_temp">Night Display Temperature</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_row_count">Quick Settings Row Count</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_row_count_desc">On Samsung TouchWiz Nougat and Oreo, it\'s possible to customize the QS layout grid with hidden settings. Use this to change the row count. Please enable this as a Persistent Option.</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_column_count">Quick Settings Column Count</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_column_count_desc">On Samsung TouchWiz Nougat and Oreo, it\'s possible to customize the QS layout grid with hidden settings. Use this to change the column count. Please enable this as a Persistent Option.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_force_enable_all">Enable All Disabled/Hidden Options</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_force_enable_all_desc">Certain options in SystemUI Tuner are hidden or disabled depending on your device and what version of Android it\'s running. Enabling this will force those options to be visible and enabled. WARNING: there\'s usually a good reason these options are disabled or hidden. They may simply not work, or they may break your device. Proceed with caution!</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_manage_qs_tiles">Manage QS Tiles</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_manage_qs_tiles_desc">Enable or disable SystemUI Tuner\'s QS tiles individually.</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_disable_high_brightness_warning">Disable High Brightness Warning</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_disable_high_brightness_warning_desc">In some regions, Samsung devices will show a warning when you attempt to go above a certain screen brightness level. This setting is usually reset on reboot. Enable this and set it as a Persistent Option to permanently disable this warning.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_editor">Quick Settings Editor</string>
    <string name="option_qs_editor_desc">While custom QS tiles are only available on Android Nougat (7.0) and later, Marshmallow (6.0) still has limited QS editing available. You can reorder, remove, and add default QS tiles, as well as basic Intents.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_fancy_anim">QS Fancy Animation</string>
    <string name="option_qs_fancy_anim_desc">On supported devices, you can use this to disable the fancy QS tile movement and fading when fully expanding the notification center. If this doesn\'t seem to have an effect on your device, keep it turned on to avoid other issues.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_move_full_rows">QS Move Full Rows</string>
    <string name="option_qs_move_full_rows_desc">What this actually does isn\'t explained very well, but it does something and you could try it if you want. It has something to do with pulling down the notification center.</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_left">Back Gesture Edge Width (Left)</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_left_desc">Android 11 introduces an option to set the sensitivity for the screen-edge back gesture by adjusting the detection area\'s width. Use this option to set the left edge\'s width more finely, or remove it altogether.</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_right">Back Gesture Edge Width (Right)</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_right_desc">Android 11 introduces an option to set the sensitivity for the screen-edge back gesture by adjusting the detection area\'s width. Use this option to set the right edge\'s width more finely, or remove it altogether.</string>
    <string name="option_hide_multi_sim_panel">Hide QS Multi-SIM Panel</string>
    <string name="option_hide_multi_sim_panel_desc">On Samsung devices, you can use this option to hide the multi-SIM view that appears in the expanded quick settings panel.</string>
    <string name="option_disable_combined_internet">Disable Combined Network Options</string>
    <string name="option_disable_combined_internet_desc">On Android 12, Google combined the settings for WiFi, Bluetooth, and cellular into one menu. The quick settings tiles for WiFi and cellular were also combined into a single Internet tile. Enabling this option will bring back the old menus in Settings and allow you to restore the separate QS tiles. You may need to reboot for this to properly take effect. If you don\'t see the WiFi and cellular tiles, you can add them using the Quick Settings Editor feature in SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="option_disable_lock_screen_ads">Disable Lock Screen Ads</string>
    <string name="option_disable_lock_screen_ads_desc">If your Kindle has ads that show on the lock screen, you can use this option to disable them. In order to make it permanent, you should enable this option in the Persistent Options screen as well.</string>
    <string name="option_allow_custom_left_lock_shortcut">Allow Custom Left Lock Screen Shortcut</string>
    <string name="option_allow_custom_left_lock_shortcut_desc">FireOS normally reserves the left lock screen shortcut for the smart device dashboard, even if you change the shortcut. Enable this here and in Persistent Options to be able to use a custom shortcut.</string>
    <string name="home_welcome_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="immersive_none">None</string>
    <string name="immersive_full">Full</string>
    <string name="immersive_status">Status</string>
    <string name="immersive_nav">Nav</string>
    <string name="immersive_blacklist">Blacklist</string>
    <string name="immersive_whitelist">Whitelist</string>
    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="all_apps">Alla appar</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Välj appar</string>
    <string name="radio">Radio</string>
    <string name="reset">Återställ</string>
    <string name="grant">Tillåt</string>
    <string name="help">Hjälp</string>
    <string name="no_root_msg">Det gick inte att bevilja behörigheter på enheten eftersom varken root- eller Shizuku-åtkomst upptäcktes. Om din enhet är rootad, se till att SystemUI Tuner har root-åtkomst. Annars trycker du på HJÄLP-knappen för ADB- och Shizuku-instruktioner.</string>
    <string name="wss_required_msg">WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS är inte tillåtet.</string>
    <string name="mode">Läge</string>
    <string name="key">Nyckel</string>
    <string name="value">Värde</string>
    <string name="label">Etikett</string>
    <string name="hide">Dölj</string>
    <string name="show">Visa</string>
    <string name="enabled">Aktiverad</string>
    <string name="enable">Aktivera</string>
    <string name="global">Global</string>
    <string name="secure">Säkert</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="left">Vänster</string>
    <string name="middle">Mitten</string>
    <string name="right">Höger</string>
    <string name="snooze_default">Standard</string>
    <string name="snooze_a">A</string>
    <string name="snooze_b">B</string>
    <string name="snooze_c">C</string>
    <string name="snooze_d">D</string>
    <string name="disabled">Inaktiverad</string>
    <string name="auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="tile_full_immersive">Fullständigt Uppslukande</string>
    <string name="tile_nav_immersive">Uppslukande Navigation</string>
    <string name="tile_status_immersive">Uppslukande Status</string>
    <string name="add">Lägg till</string>
    <string name="add_qs_tile">Lägg till QS-ruta</string>
    <string name="intent">Avsikt</string>
    <string name="view_online">Visa på Nätet</string>
    <string name="tile_custom">Anpassad</string>
    <string name="next">Nästa</string>
    <string name="finish">Slutför</string>
    <string name="previous">Föregående</string>
    <string name="exit">Avsluta</string>
    <string name="done">Klar</string>
    <string name="error">Fel</string>
    <string name="status_bar_icons">Statusfältikoner</string>
    <string name="network_states">Nätverksstater</string>
    <string name="volume_visibility">Volymsynlighet</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_visibility">Bluetooth-Synlighet</string>
    <string name="location_visibility">Platssynlighet</string>
    <string name="alarm_visibility">Alarmsynlighet</string>
    <string name="sync_visibility">Synkroniseringssynlighet</string>
    <string name="tty_visibility">TTY Visibility</string>
    <string name="eri_visibility">ERI Visibility</string>
    <string name="secure_visibility">Secure Visibility</string>
    <string name="mute_visibility">Mute Visibility</string>
    <string name="speakerphone_visibility">Speakerphone Visibility</string>
    <string name="airplane_visibility">Airplane Visibility</string>
    <string name="wifi_visibility">WiFi Visibility</string>
    <string name="mobile_visibility">Mobile Visibility</string>
    <string name="wifi_level">WiFi Level</string>
    <string name="wifi_fully_connected">WiFi Fully Connected</string>
    <string name="mobile_level">Mobile Level</string>
    <string name="mobile_fully_connected">Mobile Fully Connected</string>
    <string name="mobile_roaming">Mobile Roaming</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_type">Mobile Data Type</string>
    <string name="mobile_activity_type">Mobile Activity Type</string>
    <string name="wifi_activity_type">WiFi Activity Type</string>
    <string name="mobile_carrier_network_change">Carrier Network Change</string>
    <string name="mobile_inflate_signal">Mobile Inflate Signal</string>
    <string name="battery_level">Battery Level</string>
    <string name="battery_charging">Battery Charging</string>
    <string name="clock_time">Clock Time</string>
    <string name="status_bar_style">Status Bar Style</string>
    <string name="backup_restore">Backup/Restore</string>
    <string name="back_up">Back Up</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="set_color">Set Color</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_desc">Your Android device probably has a lot of settings to change, but did you know there\'s a lot of settings that are hidden? This app helps you change those hidden settings! You don\'t need root access, but you do have to follow a few steps to set this app up.</string>
    <string name="intro_terms">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="intro_terms_desc">Please read these terms. I promise they\'re worthwhile. For most of you, they\'ll save you an email.</string>
    <string name="intro_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="intro_disclaimer_desc">SystemUI Tuner can change hidden settings. Unfortunately, since they\'re hidden, there\'s a chance that your particular device won\'t respond to certain changes. On heavily customized versions of Android, such as EMUI, MIUI, and ColorOS, there will be a lot of features that simply don\'t work. Please keep in mind that there\'s simply nothing I can do about this.</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_wss">Grant Write Secure Settings</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_wss_desc">SystemUI Tuner needs a special permission to work. To grant it, you either need to use ADB or be rooted. Pressing GRANT below will attempt to use root to grant the permission. Otherwise, hit the HELP button, and we\'ll help you get ADB set up. Don\'t worry, though; ADB is perfectly safe to use. You won\'t void your warranty, trip Samsung Knox, root your phone, or unlock the bootloader.</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_extra">Grant Extra Permissions</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_extra_desc">For certain features, SystemUI Tuner needs some extra ADB permissions to work properly. You don\'t have to grant these now, and you\'ll be prompted if they\'re needed.</string>
    <string name="intro_system_alert_window">System Alert Window</string>
    <string name="intro_system_alert_window_desc">Android 12 and later have significantly restricted the ability for apps to run operations in the background and when the device boots. Granting SystemUI Tuner permission to display over other apps will exempt it from these restrictions and improve the reliability of Persistent Options. This permission is completely optional.</string>
    <string name="intro_allow_notifications">Allow Notifications</string>
    <string name="intro_allow_notifications_desc">Android 13 introduces a new restriction on apps requiring permission from the user to display notifications. SystemUI Tuner may show a notification when running background operations. If you would like to see this notification, please allow SystemUI Tuner to show notifications.</string>
    <string name="intro_last">Thanks for using my app!</string>
    <string name="intro_last_desc">Follow me on Mastodon or Twitter for the latest updates.</string>
    <string name="intro_crash_reports">Enable Crash Reports</string>
    <string name="intro_crash_reports_desc">You can choose to enable anonymous crash reports to help keep the app running smoothly. No personal information is collected. To fully disable collection once enabled, you\'ll need to force stop SystemUI Tuner. You can change this setting later.</string>
    <string name="crash_reports_desc">You can choose to enable anonymous crash reports to help keep the app running smoothly. No personal information is collected. To fully disable collection once enabled, you\'ll need to force stop SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_lower">Sorry, this feature only works with Android %s and later</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_both">Sorry, this feature only works from Android %1$s to Android %2$s</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_higher">Sorry, this feature only works through Android %s</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_storage">Sorry, you need an SD card to change this option.</string>
    <string name="reset_confirm">This will reset most changes made by SystemUI Tuner. The below options will have to be reset manually. I recommend that you reboot after resetting.\n%s</string>
    <string name="persistent_options_desc">Välj ett alternativ här för att låsa dess värden till de som har satts av SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="android_marshmallow">Marshmallow 6.0</string>
    <string name="android_nougat">Nougat 7.0</string>
    <string name="android_nougat_7_1">Nougat 7.1</string>
    <string name="android_oreo">Oreo 8.0</string>
    <string name="android_oreo_8_1">Oreo 8.1</string>
    <string name="android_pie">Pie 9.0</string>
    <string name="android_10">10</string>
    <string name="android_11">11</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail">Kunde inte skriva inställningen!</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail_desc">Tyvärr har Android begränsat möjligheten att ändra den här inställningen. För att arbeta runt det behöver du antingen min tilläggsapp eller Shizuku. Om du redan har tillägget installerat, kan du behöva uppdatera det. Om du redan har Shizuku installerat, se till att det körs och SystemUI Tuner har tillåtits åtkomst.</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail_get_add_on">Skaffa tillägg</string>
    <string name="download_shizuku">Skaffa Shizuku</string>
    <string name="open_shizuku">Öppna Shizuku</string>
    <string name="read_setting_fail">Kunde inte läsa inställningen!</string>
    <string name="read_setting_fail_desc">Tyvärr har Android begränsat möjligheten att läsa den här inställningen. För att arbeta runt det behöver du antingen min tilläggsapp eller Shizuku. Om du redan har tillägget installerat, kan du behöva uppdatera det. Om du redan har Shizuku installerat, se till att det körs och SystemUI Tuner har tillåtits åtkomst.</string>
    <string name="donate">Donera</string>
    <string name="donate_desc">Jag gör den här appen på min fritid. Om du tycker om att använda den, överväg att köpa mig en kopp kaffe (även om jag inte dricker kaffe). Naturligtvis är detta en donation, och du behöver inte göra någonting. Det finns inga betalväggar i SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="paypal">PayPal</string>
    <string name="google_play">Google Play</string>
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="email">E-post</string>
    <string name="website">Webbsida</string>
    <string name="more_apps">Fler appar</string>
    <string name="telegram">Telegram</string>
    <string name="mastodon">Mastodon</string>
    <string name="check_it_out">Prova det</string>
    <string name="add_custom_item">Lägg till Anpassad Objekt</string>
    <string name="edit_custom_item">Redigera Anpassad Objekt</string>
    <string name="remove_item">Ta Bort Objektet</string>
    <string name="remove_item_desc">Är du säker på att du vill ta bort detta objekt?</string>
    <string name="custom_persistent_option_summary_template">Typ av inställningar: %1$s, Nyckel: %2$s, Värde: %3$s</string>
    <string name="settings_read_template">Typ av inställningar: %1$s, Nyckel: %2$s</string>
    <string name="tile_battery">Batteri</string>
    <string name="tile_clock">Klocka</string>
    <string name="tile_demo">Demoläge</string>
    <string name="tile_heads_up">Heads-up aviseringar</string>
    <string name="tile_night_mode">Nattläge</string>
    <string name="icon_blacklist_rotation_lock">Rotationslås</string>
    <string name="icon_blacklist_rotation_lock_desc">Ändring av svartlistan kan orsaka att den här ikonen visas i ditt statusfält. Detta är ikonen för rotationslås. Du kan svartlista den nedan.</string>
    <string name="hide_battery_android_bug_msg">Att dölja batteriikonen är inte längre möjligt med hjälp av ikonsvartlistan på Android 10. Detta är ett fel i Android. Det bör rättas i Android 11.</string>
    <string name="hide_battery_android_bug_btn_view_issue">Visa Problemet</string>
    <string name="error_creating_file_template">Misslyckades att skapa filen: %s</string>
    <string name="error_restoring_icon_blacklist">Misslyckades att återställa: %s</string>
    <string name="permission_grant_success">Behörigheterna har beviljats framgångsrikt.</string>
    <string name="permission_grant_failure">Misslyckades att bevilja behörigheter. Om du har en Xiaomi eller OPPO/Realme/OnePlus-enhet, se till att du aktiverar \"USB-felsökning (säkerhetsinställningar)\" eller aktivera \"Inaktivera behörighetsövervakning\".</string>
    <string name="permission_grant_failure_short">Misslyckades att bevilja behörigheter.\n%s</string>
    <string name="patreon">Patreon</string>
    <string name="patreon_desc">För $1 varje månad får du tillgång till alla mina betalda appar och mer.</string>
    <string name="supporters">Stödjare</string>
    <string name="supporters_desc">These people help keep this app (and me) going.</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_status_bar_opaque">Opaque</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_status_bar_semi_transparent">Semi-Transparent</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_status_bar_translucent">Translucent</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_data_type_roaming">Roaming</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_data_type_none">None</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_data_type_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_data_type_not_default_data">Not Default Data</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_activity_type_none">None</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_activity_type_in">In</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_activity_type_out">Out</string>
    <string name="demo_mode_activity_type_inout">In/Out</string>
    <string name="safe_audio_state_not_configured">Not Configured</string>
    <string name="safe_audio_state_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="safe_audio_state_inactive">Inactive</string>
    <string name="safe_audio_state_active">Active</string>
    <string name="persistent_options_not_sticking_title">Options not Resetting on Boot?</string>
    <string name="persistent_options_not_sticking_desc">You may need to whitelist SystemUI Tuner from any battery optimizations. Click here to find out how.</string>
    <string name="setting_applied_dialog">Option Applied!</string>
    <string name="setting_applied_dialog_desc">Do you want to keep changes? This option will be reverted after %s seconds.</string>
    <string name="keep">Keep</string>
    <string name="revert">Revert</string>
    <string name="increase" desc="This is in verb form.">Increase</string>
    <string name="decrease" desc="This is in verb form.">Decrease</string>
    <string name="blocked_reason_read_terms">Please make sure to read the terms before continuing.</string>
    <string name="blocked_reason_write_secure_settings">SystemUI Tuner can\'t function without the Write Secure Settings permission. Tap the \"Help\" button if you\'re having trouble granting it.</string>
    <string name="blocked_reason_choose_os">Please choose an operating system before continuing.</string>
</resources>
