<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SystemUI Тунер</string>
    <string name="manager_channel">Manager (Turn Off)</string>
    <string name="tap_to_disable">Tap to disable this notification</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="category_display">Display</string>
    <string name="category_accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="category_apps">Apps</string>
    <string name="category_audio">Audio &amp; Sound</string>
    <string name="category_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="category_easter_eggs">Easter Eggs</string>
    <string name="category_network">Network</string>
    <string name="category_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="category_status_bar">Status Bar</string>
    <string name="category_oem">OEM Features</string>
    <string name="category_system">System</string>
    <string name="category_ui">UI</string>
    <string name="category_quick_settings">Quick Settings</string>
    <string name="screen_persistent">Persistent Options</string>
    <string name="category_interaction">Interaction</string>
    <string name="more">Још</string>
    <string name="tweaks">Tweaks</string>
    <string name="sub_cellular">Cellular</string>
    <string name="sub_wifi">Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="sub_miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="sub_htc">HTC</string>
    <string name="sub_huawei">Huawei/Honor</string>
    <string name="sub_lg">LG</string>
    <string name="sub_oneplus">OnePlus</string>
    <string name="sub_samsung">Samsung</string>
    <string name="sub_sony">Sony</string>
    <string name="sub_xiaomi">Xiaomi</string>
    <string name="sub_security">Security</string>
    <string name="sub_storage">Storage</string>
    <string name="sub_power">Power</string>
    <string name="add_to_blacklist">Add to Icon Blacklist</string>
    <string name="remove_from_blacklist">Remove from Icon Blacklist</string>
    <string name="sub_demo">Demo Mode</string>
    <string name="sub_demo_desc">Demo Mode allows you to force your device\'s status bar into different states. You can use it to show or hide specific icons, specify signal strengths, and a few other things.</string>
    <string name="special_sub_airplane_mode">Airplane Mode Tweaks</string>
    <string name="special_sub_airplane_mode_desc">Airplane mode automatically disables all radios on your device when it is toggled. You can specify which radios should be disabled (such as keeping WiFi on when enabling airplane mode). Also, you can change which radios can be toggled manually when the device enters airplane mode.</string>
    <string name="special_sub_icon_blacklist">Icon Blacklist</string>
    <string name="special_sub_icon_blacklist_desc">Choose specific icons to hide from the status bar. Note that this feature will not work on all devices or with all icons. Notification icons cannot be hidden using this feature.</string>
    <string name="feature_lock_timeout">Set Custom Device Lock Timeout</string>
    <string name="feature_lock_timeout_desc">Under the \"secure lock settings\", you can set an \"automatically lock\" timer. This timer determines how long after the device enters sleep mode that the lock screen should be displayed. Through this option, you can set whatever value (in milliseconds) that you want. If you set a high enough value, then essentially your lock screen will never show (provided you have disabled the \"power button instantly locks device\" feature).</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_saver_trigger">Set Custom Battery Saver Trigger Percent</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_saver_trigger_desc" formatted="false">Google\'s Battery Saver feature can automatically trigger when the battery level is at 5\% or 15\%. With this, you can set your own trigger percent.</string>
    <string name="feature_long_press_delay">Set Custom Long Press Delay</string>
    <string name="feature_long_press_delay_desc">In Accessibility settings, there\'s a feature called \"touch &amp; hold delay\" which allows you to specify how long you have to hold down on the screen for Android to recognize a long-press event. However, the only options by default are \"short\", “medium\", and \"long.\" You can set your own delay.</string>
    <string name="feature_font_scale">Set Custom Font Scale</string>
    <string name="feature_font_scale_desc">Android allows you to set the size of the text shown on your device by specifying a system-wide font scale. This value is typically represented as \"small\", \"normal\", \"large\", \"huge\", and \"extra huge.\" However, you can set your own custom value.</string>
    <string name="feature_freeform">Enable Freeform Multiwindow</string>
    <string name="feature_freeform_desc">Whether to enable freeform multiwindow support. Requires reboot. Only works on Android 7.0+ devices.</string>
    <string name="feature_app_install_location">Set Default App Install Location</string>
    <string name="feature_app_install_location_desc">Default app install location. Choose which storage apps are installed to by default. Normally, apps themselves decide by specifying the value in the AndroidManifest, but you can choose to have them install to the adoptable storage medium if you want.</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_notifications">Heads Up Notification Toggle</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_notifications_desc">Toggle to globally enable or disable heads up notifications. Heads up notifications are the notifications that pop up at the top of the screen.</string>
    <string name="feature_insufficient_storage_warning">Bypass \"Insufficient Storage Available\" Warning</string>
    <string name="feature_insufficient_storage_warning_desc">When your device reaches a certain threshold value of available storage, Android displays a warning that your device has insufficient amounts of storage available. This can prevent you from installing new apps or updates. You can manually lower the threshold value to prevent this warning from showing.</string>
    <string name="feature_keep_screen_on">Keep the Device On when Plugged In</string>
    <string name="feature_keep_screen_on_desc">In Android\'s Developer Settings, you can select the option to keep the screen on when plugged into power. By default, this enables the feature for all power sources. You can specify which power sources you want to have your phone\'s screen to stay on.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_animation_scales">Set Custom Animation Scales</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_animation_scales_desc">In Android\'s Developer Settings, you can set animation scales to control the duration of animations. If the available options are too fast or slow for you, you can set custom values here.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_rotation">Lock Screen Orientation to Custom Value</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_rotation_desc">Most phones only allow you to lock your phone\'s screen orientation to Portrait mode. With this setting, you can lock screen orientation to any orientation. You will first have to disable auto-rotate before this will work.</string>
    <string name="feature_immersive_mode">Immersive Mode</string>
    <string name="feature_immersive_mode_desc">Most other applications that allow you to toggle immersive mode only have a few options: hide the navigation bar or hide the status bar. It\'s actually possible to set this on a per-app basis, in either whitelist or blacklist mode.</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_snooze_length">Heads-Up Notification Snooze Length</string>
    <string name="feature_heads_up_snooze_length_desc">Milliseconds after a heads up notification is pushed back before the app can interrupt again. (Default: 60 seconds).</string>
    <string name="feature_camera_gestures">Camera Gestures</string>
    <string name="feature_camera_gestures_desc">Enabling this may allow your phone to quickly launch the camera by double tapping the power button or flipping the phone between back and front.</string>
    <string name="feature_disable_safe_audio_warning">Disable Safe Audio Warning</string>
    <string name="feature_disable_safe_audio_warning_desc">EU regulations require smartphones to warn when going above certain volume levels (85dB). This warning must be shown once after every reboot or after 20 hours of continuous music playback. The warning must be dismissed by the user manually, but through hidden commands you can automatically bypass the warning.</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_ui_sounds">Set Custom UI Sounds</string>
    <string name="feature_custom_ui_sounds_desc">Android has a lot of sounds for different parts of the UI. A lot of these can actually be changed to your own custom sounds. You just need to specify the file for Android to use.</string>
    <string name="feature_fix_tethering">Fix Tethering</string>
    <string name="feature_fix_tethering_desc">On some devices and Android versions, this may bypass carrier restrictions on tethering.</string>
    <string name="feature_shortcode_warning">Disable SMS Short Code Confirmation</string>
    <string name="feature_shortcode_warning_desc">When sending SMS to certain short codes, the system warns you that you may be charged a fee. You can disable that warning here.</string>
    <string name="feature_sms_limit">Custom SMS Limit</string>
    <string name="feature_sms_limit_desc">By default, Android limits you to sending 30 SMS every 30 minutes before bothering you with a pop-up notification. Using these two values, you can customize however many SMS you want to be able to send without being bothered.</string>
    <string name="feature_lockscreen_shortcuts">Lockscreen Shortcuts</string>
    <string name="feature_lockscreen_shortcuts_desc">Starting with Android Oreo Developer Preview 3, Google removed the ability to customize the lockscreen shortcuts. However, the preference value can still be set manually.</string>
    <string name="feature_enable_adb">Enable ADB</string>
    <string name="feature_enable_adb_desc">Certain devices disable ADB automatically after a period of inactivity. Enable this option and set it as a Persistent Option to force-enable ADB.</string>
    <string name="feature_dark_mode">Enable Global Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="feature_dark_mode_desc">Android Pie and 10 introduced a global dark mode option, but this option has been part of Android for a while now. This option can enable dark mode in apps that support this feature (such as Instagram). A reboot may be required for changes to take effect.</string>
    <string name="feature_clock_seconds">Show Clock Seconds</string>
    <string name="feature_clock_seconds_desc">Enable seconds in the status bar clock. This won\'t work on all devices and configurations, including MIUI and One UI.</string>
    <string name="feature_dnd_in_volume">Do Not Disturb Toggle in Volume Indicator</string>
    <string name="feature_dnd_in_volume_desc">Allows you to toggle Do Not Disturb from the volume popup.</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_percent">Show Battery Percentage in Status Bar</string>
    <string name="feature_battery_percent_desc">Shows the current battery percentage in the battery icon on the status bar. May require root to activate.</string>
    <string name="feature_header_airplane_mode_radios">Exempt</string>
    <string name="feature_header_airplane_mode_toggleable_radios">Toggleable</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_ac">On AC Power</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_usb">On USB Power</string>
    <string name="option_keep_awake_on_wireless">On Wireless Power</string>
    <string name="option_animator_duration_scale">Animator Duration Scale</string>
    <string name="option_window_animation_scale">Window Animation Scale</string>
    <string name="option_transition_animation_scale">Transition Animation Scale</string>
    <string name="option_storage_threshold_percentage">Storage Threshold Percentage</string>
    <string name="option_storage_threshold_max_bytes">Storage Threshold Max Bytes</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture_double_power">Double-Tap Power Button</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture">Gesture</string>
    <string name="option_camera_gesture_twist">Flip Phone Back and Forth</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_cell">Cell</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_bluetooth">Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_wifi">WiFi</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_nfc">NFC</string>
    <string name="option_airplane_mode_radio_wimax">WiMax</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_internal">Internal Storage</string>
    <string name="option_app_install_location_sd">SD Card</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_0">Portrait</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_90">Landscape CCW</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_180">Portrait Inverse</string>
    <string name="option_user_rotation_270">Landscape CW</string>
    <string name="option_sms_limit_count">Max Send Count</string>
    <string name="option_sms_limit_interval">Time Interval</string>
    <string name="option_lockscreen_shortcut_left">Left Shortcut</string>
    <string name="option_lockscreen_shortcut_right">Right Shortcut</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_dock">Car Dock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_dock_desc">Audio that is played when the phone is docked in a car dock.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_undock">Car Undock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_car_undock_desc">Audio that is played when the phone is removed from a car dock.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_dock">Desk Dock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_dock_desc">Audio that is played when the phone is docked in a desk dock.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_undock">Desk Undock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_desk_undock_desc">Audio that is played when the phone is removed from a desk dock.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_lock">Lock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_lock_desc">Audio that is played when the phone is locked.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_unlock">Unlock</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_unlock_desc">Audio that is played when the device is unlocked.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_low_battery">Low Battery</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_low_battery_desc">Audio that is played when the device is at low battery.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_trusted">Trusted</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_trusted_desc">Audio that is played when the device enters the “trusted” state without unlocking.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_wireless_charging">Charging</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_wireless_charging_desc">Audio that is played when the device is being charged.</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_disable_charging">Disable Charging Sound</string>
    <string name="option_ui_sound_disable_charging_desc">Whether to disable the sound that plays when the device begins charging.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_read_setting">Read Custom Setting</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_read_setting_desc">If you know the key to a particular setting, you can use this to see its current value.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_write_setting">Write Custom Setting</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_write_setting_desc">If you have a particular setting you want to change that isn\'t part of SystemUI Tuner, you can set it here.</string>
    <string name="option_qqs_tiles">Quick Settings Header Count</string>
    <string name="option_qqs_tiles_desc">Android Nougat introduced a new quick settings feature, called the Quick Settings Header, that shows the first few quick settings tiles in a single row in the notification shade. Using this option, it\'s possible to increase or decrease the number of tiles shown in that row.</string>
    <string name="option_oneui_clock_position">Clock Position</string>
    <string name="option_oneui_clock_position_desc">On Samsung\'s One UI (Android Pie or later), it\'s possible to change the status bar clock position. Good Lock\'s QuickStar will let you do it, but the options are sometimes limited depending on the device. You can use this to set it to left, middle, or right. Be aware that on One UI 2.0 (Android 10), you need QuickStar to be installed for this option to have an effect. Alternatively, you can use OneUI Tuner. To make this option persistent, enable Icon Blacklist in Persistent Options.</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_navbar_color">Navigation Bar Color</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_navbar_color_desc">On Samsung Experience and One UI it\'s possible to set the navigation bar color to your own custom color. Use this option to do that.</string>
    <string name="option_custom_notification_snooze_times">Custom Notification Snooze Times</string>
    <string name="option_custom_notification_snooze_times_desc">Android Oreo 8.1 introduced an option to snooze notifications. You can use this setting to set custom values for the snooze times.</string>
    <string name="option_night_mode">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="option_night_mode_desc">Android Nougat introduced a native option to tint the display yellow at night, aptly called Night Mode. It was further refined in Nougat 7.1, and renamed to Night Display. You can enable it here and adjust different options. WARNING: On some Android 10 devices, activating this will cause the screen to go black!</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_row_count">Quick Settings Row Count</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_row_count_desc">On Samsung TouchWiz Nougat and Oreo, it\'s possible to customize the QS layout grid with hidden settings. Use this to change the row count. Please enable this as a Persistent Option.</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_column_count">Quick Settings Column Count</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_qs_column_count_desc">On Samsung TouchWiz Nougat and Oreo, it\'s possible to customize the QS layout grid with hidden settings. Use this to change the column count. Please enable this as a Persistent Option.</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_force_enable_all">Enable All Disabled/Hidden Options</string>
    <string name="option_advanced_force_enable_all_desc">Certain options in SystemUI Tuner are hidden or disabled depending on your device and what version of Android it\'s running. Enabling this will force those options to be visible and enabled. WARNING: there\'s usually a good reason these options are disabled or hidden. They may simply not work, or they may break your device. Proceed with caution!</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_disable_high_brightness_warning">Disable High Brightness Warning</string>
    <string name="option_touchwiz_disable_high_brightness_warning_desc">In some regions, Samsung devices will show a warning when you attempt to go above a certain screen brightness level. This setting is usually reset on reboot. Enable this and set it as a Persistent Option to permanently disable this warning.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_editor">Quick Settings Editor</string>
    <string name="option_qs_editor_desc">While custom QS tiles are only available on Android Nougat (7.0) and later, Marshmallow (6.0) still has limited QS editing available. You can reorder, remove, and add default QS tiles, as well as basic Intents.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_fancy_anim">QS Fancy Animation</string>
    <string name="option_qs_fancy_anim_desc">On supported devices, you can use this to disable the fancy QS tile movement and fading when fully expanding the notification center. If this doesn\'t seem to have an effect on your device, keep it turned on to avoid other issues.</string>
    <string name="option_qs_move_full_rows">QS Move Full Rows</string>
    <string name="option_qs_move_full_rows_desc">What this actually does isn\'t explained very well, but it does something and you could try it if you want. It has something to do with pulling down the notification center.</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_left">Back Gesture Edge Width (Left)</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_left_desc">Android 11 introduces an option to set the sensitivity for the screen-edge back gesture by adjusting the detection area\'s width. Use this option to set the left edge\'s width more finely, or remove it altogether.</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_right">Back Gesture Edge Width (Right)</string>
    <string name="option_back_gesture_inset_scale_right_desc">Android 11 introduces an option to set the sensitivity for the screen-edge back gesture by adjusting the detection area\'s width. Use this option to set the right edge\'s width more finely, or remove it altogether.</string>
    <string name="home_welcome_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="immersive_none">None</string>
    <string name="immersive_full">Full</string>
    <string name="immersive_status">Status</string>
    <string name="immersive_nav">Nav</string>
    <string name="immersive_blacklist">Blacklist</string>
    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="all_apps">All Apps</string>
    <string name="select_apps">Select Apps</string>
    <string name="radio">Radio</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="grant">Grant</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="no_root_title">No Root</string>
    <string name="no_root_msg">Root wasn\'t detected. If your device is rooted, make sure SystemUI Tuner has root access. Otherwise, press the HELP button for ADB instructions.</string>
    <string name="wss_required_msg">WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS isn\'t granted.</string>
    <string name="mode">Mode</string>
    <string name="key">Key</string>
    <string name="value">Value</string>
    <string name="label">Label</string>
    <string name="hide">Hide</string>
    <string name="show">Прикажи</string>
    <string name="enabled">Омогућено</string>
    <string name="global">Глобално</string>
    <string name="secure">Обезбеди</string>
    <string name="system">Систем</string>
    <string name="left">Left</string>
    <string name="middle">Middle</string>
    <string name="right">Right</string>
    <string name="snooze_default">Default</string>
    <string name="snooze_a">A</string>
    <string name="snooze_b">B</string>
    <string name="snooze_c">C</string>
    <string name="snooze_d">D</string>
    <string name="disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="tile_full_immersive">Full Immersive</string>
    <string name="tile_nav_immersive">Nav Immersive</string>
    <string name="tile_status_immersive">Status Immersive</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="add_qs_tile">Add QS Tile</string>
    <string name="intent">Intent</string>
    <string name="view_online">View Online</string>
    <string name="status_bar_icons">Status Bar Icons</string>
    <string name="network_states">Network States</string>
    <string name="volume_visibility">Volume Visibility</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_visibility">Bluetooth Visibility</string>
    <string name="location_visibility">Location Visibility</string>
    <string name="alarm_visibility">Alarm Visibility</string>
    <string name="sync_visibility">Sync Visibility</string>
    <string name="tty_visibility">TTY Visibility</string>
    <string name="eri_visibility">ERI Visibility</string>
    <string name="secure_visibility">Secure Visibility</string>
    <string name="mute_visibility">Mute Visibility</string>
    <string name="speakerphone_visibility">Speakerphone Visibility</string>
    <string name="airplane_visibility">Airplane Visibility</string>
    <string name="wifi_visibility">WiFi Visibility</string>
    <string name="mobile_visibility">Mobile Visibility</string>
    <string name="wifi_level">WiFi Level</string>
    <string name="wifi_fully_connected">WiFi Fully Connected</string>
    <string name="mobile_level">Mobile Level</string>
    <string name="mobile_fully_connected">Mobile Fully Connected</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_type">Mobile Data Type</string>
    <string name="battery_level">Battery Level</string>
    <string name="battery_charging">Батерија се пуни</string>
    <string name="clock_time">Clock Time</string>
    <string name="status_bar_style">Стил статусне траке</string>
    <string name="backup_restore">Backup/Restore</string>
    <string name="back_up">Back Up</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="set_color">Set Color</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome_desc">Your Android device probably has a lot of settings to change, but did you know there\'s a lot of settings that are hidden? This app helps you change those hidden settings! You don\'t need root access, but you do have to follow a few steps to set this app up.</string>
    <string name="intro_terms">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="intro_terms_desc">Please read these terms. I promise they\'re worthwhile. For most of you, they\'ll save you an email.</string>
    <string name="intro_disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="intro_disclaimer_desc">SystemUI Tuner can change hidden settings. Unfortunately, since they\'re hidden, there\'s a chance that your particular device won\'t respond to certain changes. On heavily customized versions of Android, such as EMUI, MIUI, and ColorOS, there will be a lot of features that simply don\'t work. Please keep in mind that there\'s simply nothing I can do about this.</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_wss">Grant Write Secure Settings</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_wss_desc">SystemUI Tuner needs a special permission to work. To grant it, you either need to use ADB or be rooted. Pressing GRANT below will attempt to use root to grant the permission. Otherwise, hit the HELP button, and we\'ll help you get ADB set up. Don\'t worry, though; ADB is perfectly safe to use. You won\'t void your warranty, trip Samsung Knox, root your phone, or unlock the bootloader.</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_extra">Grant Extra Permissions</string>
    <string name="intro_grant_extra_desc">For certain features, SystemUI Tuner needs some extra ADB permissions to work properly. You don\'t have to grant these now, and you\'ll be prompted if they\'re needed.</string>
    <string name="intro_last">Thanks for using my app!</string>
    <string name="intro_last_desc">Follow me on Twitter for the latest updates.</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_lower">Sorry, this feature only works with Android %s and later</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_both">Sorry, this feature only works from Android %1$s to Android %2$s</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_higher">Sorry, this feature only works through Android %s</string>
    <string name="compatibility_message_storage">Sorry, you need an SD card to change this option.</string>
    <string name="reset_confirm">This will reset most changes made by SystemUI Tuner. The below options will have to be reset manually. I recommend that you reboot after resetting.\n%s</string>
    <string name="persistent_options_desc">Select an option here to lock its values to those that have been set by SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="android_marshmallow">Marshmallow 6.0</string>
    <string name="android_nougat">Nougat 7.0</string>
    <string name="android_nougat_7_1">Nougat 7.1</string>
    <string name="android_oreo">Oreo 8.0</string>
    <string name="android_oreo_8_1">Oreo 8.1</string>
    <string name="android_pie">Pie 9.0</string>
    <string name="android_10">10</string>
    <string name="android_11">11</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail">Failed to write to Settings.System!</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail_desc">Unfortunately, Android added some restrictions as to what can be written to Settings.System, and it seems like you\'ve hit one of those restricted settings. Luckily, there is a way around this restriction, through the use of an add-on app. You\'ll have to download it from XDA Labs, but it is free and open source.</string>
    <string name="write_system_fail_get_add_on">Get Add-On</string>
    <string name="donate">Донирајте</string>
    <string name="donate_desc">I make this app in my free time. If you enjoy using it, consider buying me a cup of coffee (even though I don\'t drink coffee). Of course, this is a donation, and you don\'t have to do anything. There are no pay-walled features in SystemUI Tuner.</string>
    <string name="paypal">PayPal</string>
    <string name="google_play">Google Play</string>
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="more_apps">More Apps</string>
    <string name="telegram">Telegram</string>
    <string name="oneui_tuner">OneUI Tuner</string>
    <string name="oneui_tuner_desc">If you have a Samsung device running Android Pie or later on Samsung\'s One UI, you may have noticed that some options that worked on Oreo no longer work, such as Clock Seconds. I\'ve made a separate app that makes use of system overlays to bring back some of these options. It doesn\'t need root or ADB.</string>
    <string name="check_it_out">Check it Out</string>
    <string name="add_custom_item">Add Custom Item</string>
    <string name="edit_custom_item">Edit Custom Item</string>
    <string name="remove_item">Remove This Item</string>
    <string name="remove_item_desc">Are you sure you want to remove this item?</string>
    <string name="custom_persistent_option_summary_template">Settings Type: %s, Key: %s, Value: %s</string>
    <string name="tile_battery">Battery</string>
    <string name="tile_clock">Clock</string>
    <string name="tile_demo">Demo Mode</string>
    <string name="tile_heads_up">Heads Up Notifications</string>
    <string name="tile_night_mode">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="icon_blacklist_rotation_lock">Rotation Lock</string>
    <string name="icon_blacklist_rotation_lock_desc">Modifying the icon blacklist may cause the icon shown here to show up in your status bar. This is the Rotation Lock icon. You can blacklist it below.</string>
    <string name="hide_battery_android_bug_msg">Hiding the battery icon is no longer possible using the icon blacklist on Android 10. This is a bug in Android. It should be fixed in Android 11.</string>
    <string name="hide_battery_android_bug_btn_view_issue">View Issue</string>
    <string name="error_creating_file_template">Error creating file: %s</string>
    <string name="error_restoring_icon_blacklist">Error restoring: %s</string>
</resources>
