<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="adb_intro_title">ADB Guide</string>
    <string name="adb_intro_desc">Don\'t know how to use ADB? No problem. Just follow this guide and you should be set. (Note that you will need a computer for this process.)</string>
    <string name="adb_intro_desc_no_computer">Don\'t know how to use ADB? No problem. Just follow this guide and you should be set.</string>
    <string name="adb_choose_computer_os">Choose your Operating System.</string>
    <string name="adb_choose_computer_os_desc">Which operating system is your computer running?</string>
    <string name="adb_android_guide">Initial Setup (On Your Phone)</string>
    <string name="adb_final_title">تم للكل</string>
    <string name="adb_final_desc">That\'s all! If everything went well, the permission(s) should now be granted.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_1">Open the Settings app and scroll down to About Phone. Tap it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_2">Depending on your device, you may see a menu called \"Software Information\". If so, tap it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_3">Now, find the option labeled \"Build Number\". On some devices, this may simply be called \"Version\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_4">Tap that option 7 times to enable Developer Mode. You may need to enter your passcode to enable it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_5">Now, go back to the main Settings page.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_6">Depending on your device, you may see a new menu called \"Developer Options\". If so, tap it and skip the next step.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_7">If you don\'t see the Developer Options menu, find the menu labeled either \"System\" or \"Additional Settings\". You should see the Developer Options menu inside that.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_8">Scroll down until you find the switch labeled \"USB Debugging\" and enable it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_9">On Xiaomi phones, you\'ll also need to find and disable the option labeled \"USB Debugging (Security Settings)\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_10">On OPPO, Realme, and OnePlus phones, you\'ll also need to find and enable the option labeled \"Disable Permission Monitoring\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_11">Now, plug your phone into your computer. If a confirmation popup about USB Debugging appears, allow it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_android_12">Once that\'s done, it\'s time to continue on your computer.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_local_1"><![CDATA[Download and install the Shizuku app from the [Google Play Store](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=moe.shizuku.privileged.api).]]></string>
    <string name="adb_install_local_2">Open the Shizuku app and follow the instructions under \"Start via Wireless Debugging\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_local_3">Close this screen and tap the \"GRANT\" button.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_windows_1">Download the ADB ZIP from here: https://dl.google.com/android/repository/platform-tools-latest-windows.zip</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_windows_2">Extract the ZIP to a convenient location, such as `C:\\adb`.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_windows_3">Use the file explorer to browse to the extracted ZIP. You should see a bunch of files, including one called \"adb\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_windows_4">Click inside the search bar and replace what\'s there with \"cmd\" (without quotes). Then hit Enter.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_mac_1">Download the ADB ZIP from here: https://dl.google.com/android/repository/platform-tools-latest-darwin.zip</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_mac_2">Extract the ZIP to a convenient location, such as the Desktop.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_mac_3">Now, open the terminal. You can do so by pressing CMD+SPACE at the same time to open Spotlight Search, and searching for \"Terminal\".</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_mac_4">Now, browse to the extracted files using the following command: `cd /path/to/files/`. For example, if your username is Zachary and you extracted the ZIP to your desktop, the command would be `cd /Users/Zachary/Desktop/platform-tools/`, where \"platform-tools\" is the folder with the file named \"adb\" inside.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_debian_1">Open a terminal by pressing CTRL+ALT+T.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_debian_2">Install ADB with the following command: `sudo apt install android-tools-adb android-tools-fastboot`.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_fedora_1">Open a terminal.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_fedora_2">Install ADB with the following command: `sudo dnf install adb`.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_rhel_1">Open a terminal.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_rhel_2">Install ADB with the following command: `yum install android-tools`.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_linux_other_1">Download the ADB ZIP from here: https://dl.google.com/android/repository/platform-tools-latest-linux.zip</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_linux_other_2">Extract the ZIP to a convenient location, such as your Home directory.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_linux_other_3">Open a terminal.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_linux_other_4">Now, browse to the extracted files using the following command: `cd /path/to/files/`. For example, if your username is Zachary and you extracted the ZIP to your Home directory, the command would be `cd /home/Zachary/platform-tools/`, where \"platform-tools\" is the folder with the file named \"adb\" inside.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_general_end_1">A Command Prompt or Terminal window should open. Type the following command(s) inside it, and hit Enter/Return after each one. If a popup appears on your phone about USB Debugging, make sure to allow it.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_general_end_2">If everything\'s gone right, there should be no output from the commands. If there is, make sure to scroll all the way up to where you entered the command to see the error.</string>
    <string name="adb_install_adb_general_end_3">The permissions should now be granted!</string>
    <string name="adb_windows">Windows</string>
    <string name="adb_mac">macOS</string>
    <string name="adb_linux_fedora">Fedora/SUSE</string>
    <string name="adb_linux_debian">Debian/Ubuntu</string>
    <string name="adb_linux_rhel">RHEL/CentOS</string>
    <string name="adb_linux_other">Linux (Other)</string>
    <string name="adb_local">Android (This Device)</string>
</resources>
